question_data = [{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The average woman is 5 inches (13 centimeters) shorter than the average man.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
